xhtmljunction.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy of XHTMLJunction – PSD to HTML Conversion Company

The Junction Of Perfection

## This Privacy Policy does not describe the ways in which XHTMLjunction may collect or use information obtained through means other than the xhtmljunction.com website. Any questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to support(at)xhtmljunction.com. 

### Collection and Use of Information

XHTMLjunction.com may collect and store information that you voluntarily supply either while on the xhtmljunction.com website or in responding, via email, to a feature provided on the XHTMLjunction.com website. If you decide not to supply or provide XHTMLjunction.com with certain information while using the website, XHTMLjunction.com may not be able to provide you with some services that are dependent on the collection of this information. 

### Information Sharing with Third Parties

To make the site more valuable to our visitors, occasionally we may offer some additional features in conjunction with other third party service providers. Accordingly, we may make your information available to these third party service providers.

XHTMLjunction.com will not disclose the information that it collects online from you to allow third parties to use such information to mail or email other promotional offers directly to you unless you have permitted XHTMLjunction.com to disclose such information for the purposes of receiving promotional offers from such third parties. If you choose to receive these promotional offers, then your information may be used for direct mail or email marketing.

In addition, the XHTMLjunction.com website includes links to other sites and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies are separate from this Privacy Policy. When you provide information in the course of obtaining third party products or services through XHTMLjunction.com, the use of any information you provide may be governed by the privacy policy of the provider of those third party products or services, even if it appears that you are on xhtmljunction-branded pages throughout the transaction. The third party provider's privacy policy may differ from ours and you should contact the third party provider if you have any questions about its privacy practices. Please take special care at all times to be aware of which privacy policy governs your activity on the Internet.

### Protection of Your Information

All information gathered on our site is stored within a XHTMLjunction.com-controlled database accessible only to XHTMLjunction.com. However, as effective as any security measure may be, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We are continually making changes and improvements to the services we offer through XHTMLjunction.com. If we need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, we will post the changes before they take effect. If you have any questions about the XHTMLjunction.com Privacy Policy, please contact support at **[support(at)xhtmljunction.com](mailto:support@xhtmljunction.com)**.
